A Guide to the WAGE Radio Collection, 1958-2003
Thomas Balch Library
Thomas Balch Library
WAGE Radio Collection 1958-2003
Thomas Balch Library
M 083, AV 006, OMB 017, VC 0053
This collection consists of documents, photographs, and WAGE Radio broadcast recordings, including reporting on local news and events, local sports, politics, and international affairs. Many of the recordings on international affairs were hosted by news director William Chewning III. The radio broadcast recordings were recorded on 1/4" analog reel to reel tapes and include end of the year actuality compilations (edited sound bites of broadcast journalists), broadcast highlights, news reports, and reports on events of local significance. The majority of the recordings are from the 1970s and 1980s with some recordings from the late 1950s, 1960s, and early 1990s. There are a total of 482 reel to reel tape recordings in the collection. The WAGE radio recordings are only accessible in digital format (.wav and mp3 format), which will be transferred to a CD on request for in-library use. Included in the collection are several pieces of equipment used by WAGE Radio to produce and present programs. There are also various photographs and other visual materials of WAGE Radio sponsored and related events, including photos of home and trade shows and a 16" by 20" framed collage. There are also documents and records of WAGE material and WAGE media in the manuscript and oversized materials including correspondence, Crystal Radio Award documents, newspaper articles, advertisements, and event posters.
WAGE Radio
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection open for research.
Acquisition Information
William Chewning III, Fredericksburg, VA; Claire Kincannon, Paeonian Springs, VA; New World Radio, Falls Church, VA
Alternative Form Available
Sound recordings: reel to reel tapes; digital files: (.wav & .mp3 format).
Accruals
1998.0001; 2009.0100; 2010.0274; 2010.0374
Historical Information
On 6 March 1958, WAGE Radio went on the air as Loudoun County's first and only radio station. The station, located in Leesburg, was originally available on 1290 kHz AM frequency. Many notable personalities influenced and developed WAGE Radio over the years, including William H. Spencer, Jr. (28 February 1917-23 October 2007), John R. Gill (21 September 1917-30 November 2002), William J. Chewning III (14 May 1931-13 May 2008), and Paul Draisey (26 April 1956-16 April 2012).
William H. Spencer Jr. was general manager of WAGE from 1964-1988. John Gill was chief promotion director and an engineer at WAGE when the station first began broadcasting. William Chewning III was a news director and journalist at WAGE during the 1970s. He hosted international specials on current events, cultures, and political issues of countries and regions, including China, Cuba, Russia, Kenya, Vietnam, United Kingdom, Africa, and the Middle East. Paul Draisey began working at WAGE Radio in 1971 and was 14 when he aired his first show. Often called the "Voice of Loudoun," he worked for WAGE from 1971-2007 as a reporter and general manager. During his time at WAGE, Draisey hosted a popular afternoon show called "The Drive Home with Paul Draisey."
WAGE Radio was a daytime radio station with an emphasis on local news. In 1995, WAGE moved to 1200 kHz AM frequency which allowed the station access to a stronger, full-time signal. With the change in frequencies came a change in format, and WAGE became a twenty-four hour news and talk radio station and included nationally syndicated programs. WAGE continued its commitment to local news and events, however, and covered local events, births, weddings, deaths, weather, traffic reports, agriculture, sports, and even birthdays
New World Radio (WUST), a broadcast facility that focuses on foreign language programs for Washington D.C.'s international communities, acquired the station in 2005. In 2007 much of the staff was fired and many of the local news programs were eliminated. New World Radio cited economic pressure as a primary reason for the firings. In 2008, WAGE received a permit to move to 1190 kHz frequency and increase its power to 50,000 watts, amking it a much more powerful station with a regional broadcast area. Before it was able to implement these changes, however, WAGE was forced to go off the air as a result of economic conditions, specifically decreased local ad revenue. WAGE was off air from 2 August 2009 until 2011. On 11 April 2011, a re-branded WAGE went back on air as WCRW, "China Radio International," with programs and entertainment from the Pacific Rim. WCRW made significant changes to the station's programming and places little focus on providing local news and events, looking instead to the emerging Asian market in Northern Virginia.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of documents, photographs, and WAGE Radio broadcast recordings, including reporting on local news and events, local sports, politics, and international affairs. Many of the recordings on international affairs were hosted by news director William Chewning III. The radio broadcast recordings were recorded on 1/4" analog reel to reel tapes and include end of the year actuality compilations (edited sound bites of broadcast journalists), broadcast highlights, news reports, and reports on events of local significance. The majority of the recordings are from the 1970s and 1980s with some recordings from the late 1950s, 1960s, and early 1990s. There are a total of 482 reel to reel tape recordings in the collection. The WAGE radio recordings are only accessible in digital format (.wav and mp3 format), which will be transferred to a CD on request for in-library use. The date of each broadcast (if available) is included in the container list. Included in the collection are several pieces of equipment used by WAGE Radio to produce and present programs. There are also various photographs and other visual materials of WAGE Radio sponsored and related events, including photos of home and trade shows and a 16" by 20" framed collage. There are also documents and records of WAGE material and WAGE media in the manuscript and oversized materials including correspondence, Crystal Radio Award documents, newspaper articles, advertisements, and event posters.
Arrangement
Box: folder
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Bibliography
Dulles District.com, For Those Who Never Knew WAGE, http://dullesdistrict.com/?q=content/those-who-never-knew-wage (accessed 9 August 2012).
Leesburg Today, 17 April 2011, http://www.leesburgtoday.com/news/article_4b8cf6aa-88c5-11e1-9288-001a4bcf887a.html (accessed 27 November 2012).
Loudoun Times-Mirror, 21 July 1988, Thomas Balch Library, Leesburg, VA.
Loudoun Times-Mirror, 24 November 1988, Thomas Balch Library, Leesburg, VA.
Loudoun Times-Mirror, 13 April 2011, http://www.loudountimes.com/index.php/news/article/wage_orients_itself_to_asian_market/, (accessed 27 November 2012).
New World Radio, http://www.wust1120.com/WUST/Welcome.html (accessed 10 June 2013).
Washington Post, 16 May 2008, http://www.washingtonpost.com (accessed 27 November 2012).
Washington Post, 16 August 2009, http://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/content/article/2009/08/11/AR2009081103541.html (accessed 27 November 2012).
Washington Post, 19 April 2012, http://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/the-state-of-nova/post/paul-draisey-voice-of-loudoun-county-dies-at-55/2012/04/19/gIQACLIPST_blog.html (accessed 9 August 2012).
WCRW, http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/WCRW (accessed 27 November 2012).
Other Finding Aid
None
Technical Requirements
CD player or computer
Related Material
Black History Committee Oral History Project 2000-2006 (M 012); Loudoun Laurels Collection, 2008- (M 045); Student Oral History Collection, 1981 (M 008), Thomas Balch Library, Leesburg, VA; Golightly, Steve, Manifest Infamy, Baltimore, MD, 2007 (V REF FICTION GOL).
Contents List
- (M 083)
    - National Defense Emergency Authorization, February 1954
    - Telegrams, February-March 1958
    - First Day Operation Logs, 6 March 1958
    - Correspondence, 1961-1993
    - Jane's Kindergarten Thank You Letters, March 1968
    - WAGE Radio Roster
    - Crystal Radio Award 1987-Overview
    - Crystal Radio Award 1987-Highlights
    - Crystal Radio Award 1987-Program Logs
    - Crystal Radio Award 1987-Community Involvement
    - Crystal Radio Award 1987-Press Clips
    - Crystal Radio Award 1987-Staff
    - Crystal Radio Award 1987-Letters
    - Crystal Radio Award 1988-Overview
    - Crystal Radio Award 1988-Letters
    - Crystal Radio Award 1988-Photos
    - Crystal Radio Award 1988-Press Clips
    - Crystal Radio Award 1988-"Why We Shine!"
    - June 1972 Flood Photographs
    - WAGE Event Photographs, 1987-1988
    - Federal Aviation Agency Photographs
    - WAGE Station Photographs
    - Miscellaneous Photographs
    - Negatives and Slides
    - Radio Active, October 1980
    - Memorabilia
    - Equipment:
      Bogen Challenger CHS-35 public address amplifier
      Juliette speaker
      Otari MX-5050 reel to reel
      Sony Tapecorder TC-250A
      Wollensak T-1500 reel to reel recorder
- (AV 006)
  - Recordings (titles taken directly from reel-to-reel tape boxes)
    - "Landslide for a President" Wage News/UPI (1972 Gen/Election), 1 November 1972
    - UPI Interviews from East Africa, Dr. David Weston & Ted Goss, 1 January 1974
    - UPI Reflection Programs "Mexico" Travel World in 1976, 1 January 1976
    - Wage Leadline, Store of the Year: Death of Howard Hughes, 5 April 1976
    - UPI Round Table "African Ark" Chewning w/Prickett (Kenya), 1 January 1977
    - UPI Round Table "East Africa Game Park Protection - Ted Goss, 1 January 1977
    - UPI Round Table "East Africa", 28 1/2 minutes plus 3 P.S.A.s, 1 January 1977
    - UPI Round Table "East Africa", 28 1/2 minutes plus 3 P.S.A.s, 1 January 1977
    - WAGE Leadline, Store of the Year: Death of Howard Hughes, 1 January 1977
    - Know Your County, U.S. Foreign Policy Review w/ Bill Chewning, 3 July 1977
    - China Slide Show w/out Music Audio, 1 January 1978
    - CNI Podium, Red China 1978, part 2, 1 January 1978
    - CNI Podium, Red China 1978, part 2, 1 January 1978
    - Slide Show, CNI News, "China 1978", 1 January 1978
    - CNI Podium, "National Public Radio" Frank Mankiewicz, 15 January 1978
    - CNI Podium, "The Mid-East" Nicholas Veliotes - State Dept, 22 January 1978
    - CNI Podium, "State of U.S. Foreign Affairs" Warren Christopher, 29 January 1978
    - CNI Podium, "Salt II" Paul C. Warnke - Washington, D.C., 5 February 1978
    - CNI Podium, "Dateline Cuba," 26 February 1978
    - CNI Podium, "Dateline Cuba", 26 February 1978
    - CNI Podium, "Israel's 30 years" Begin, Meir & Sadat, 1 April 1978
    - CNI Podium, "Museum of Africa", 5/78, Dr. Luwel/Brussels, Belgium, 1 May 1978
    - CNI Podium, "Museum of Africa", 5/78, Dr. Luwel/Brussels (Updated Version), 1 May 1978
    - CNI Podium, Israel's 30 years with Bill Chewning, 10 June 1978
    - CNI Podium, Peoples Republic of China, 1 July 1978
    - CNI Podium, Peoples Republic of China, 1 July 1978
    - PRC China Cuts, July 1978 (cuts), 2 actualities & 1 voicer wrap, 1 July 1978
    - PRC China Cuts, July 1978 (cuts), 2 actualities and 1 voicer wrap, 1 July 1978
    - Commune Interview Chengtu PRC CNI News for the USDA, 3 July 1978
    - CNI Audio Track, China 1978, without music, 1 August 1978
    - CNI Podium, Betty Ford, 13 December 1978
    - CNI Podium, Travel and Cruise 79, Noice, Largomarcini, Thomsche, 1 January 1979
    - CNI Podium, Offshore Drilling off N.J. Bill C. and Dan Price, 14 January 1979
    - CNI Podium, President Carter, CNI World News Service, 24 February 1979
    - CBC and BBC Cuts from 3-1979, Barbados, 1 March 1979
    - CNI Podium, 3-4-79 Salt II, Warnke and Graham, 4 March 1979
    - Public Policy Forum, "China-U.S. Relations", 5 May 1979
    - CNI Broadcast special, 9-22-79 Walheim and q.a., 22 September 1979
    - CNI Podium, (Kurt Waldheim) UN from UN in N.Y., 22 September 1979
    - CNI Podium/Cuban Radio News, 6 October 1979
    - CNI Podium with Donald McHenry, United Nations Ambassador/AT State, 22 March 1980
    - CNI Podium with H.M. Saunders, 3-30-80 Mid East, 30 March 1980
    - Central Kingdom Express slide show master/w music, 1 November 1979
    - C.K.E. Slide Sound Track (master) with music (CNI World N), 1 November 1980
    - CNI International Spotlight, Bill Chewning/R.J. Moore for use in October or Early November 1980 (Elephant Project E/Africa), 1 November 1980
    - CNI Podium, Secretary of State, Haig, 1 November 1981
    - 1. Music for an October Afternoon. 2. Music for a Winter Train Ride, n.d.
  - Recordings (titles taken directly from reel-to-reel tape boxes)
    - First Washington International Horse Show/Nixon Kruschev Moscow, 1 January 1958
    - Hoof and Horn Show 1958, 1 January 1958
    - Hoof and Horn Shows 1958, 1 January 1958
    - Old Hoof and Horn, 1 March 1958
    - Upperville 1959 WAGE Coverage, 1 January 1959
    - Kennedy-Nixon Debates, 1 January 1960
    - JFK, 1 January 1963
    - Henry Ford, 17 March 1963
    - Broadcast Special J.F. Kennedy. WAGE News/Bill Chewning, 31 December 1963
    - Robert F. Kennedy Obituary and Background, not by Chewning, 1 June 1968
    - Dublin Spring Horse Show, 1971, 1 January 1971
    - Africa, 1 January 1974
    - The Climb of Mt. Kilimanjaro 1974, 1 January 1974
    - Bill Chewning Reports from Africa, July and August, 1 July 1974
    - S.G.'s statement at UNA seminar, 17 September 1974
    - Mexico 1976 Interview with Hans Tomsche, 1 January 1976
    - Bishop Yona Okoth of Uganda, 1977, Interview with Chewning, 1 January 1977
    - Interview at the Ark/East Africa, 1 January 1977
    - Interview with Bishop Yona Okoth of Uganda after his escape, 1 January 1977
    - Bank of Virginia [inside label: Virginia Gold Cup, May 4, 1985], 1 April 1977
    - Chewning Obituary (Tribute 8-26-77), 26 August 1977
    - Actuality Cuts: Rabin, Ben-Gurion, Begin, Sadat, Meir, Ect. [sic], 1 January 1978
    - China, 1 January 1978
    - State Department (#1 Bunker), 1 January 1978
    - State Department (#1 W C Harrop Africa), 1 January 1978
    - State Department (#1 Warren Christopher), 1 January 1978
    - Wardon Naiguran (Masi Mara) Kenya Ark Interview, Kenya 1978), 1 January 1978
    - Commune Interview Cheng-Tu P.R.C. CNI News for the USDA 2 of 2 3 July 1978
    - Know Your County (1978 China Trip)(Chewning/Anderson and Gonseth), 30 July 1978
    - Raw tape from United Nations with Waldheim, 1 January 1979
    - TMI Report from White House and The Boston goes to China, 1 April 1979
    - CNI Podium, (Normalization 243) China, 2 September 1979
    - CNI Podium, part 1 of 2, Central Kingdom Ex, 27 January 1980
    - Loudoun County Magazine with Chewning for use March 6, 1983; 25 years of news service to Loudoun, 8 March 1983
    - Borobudur Master Tape, 28 October 1983
    - The Forum with Chewning, Historic District, 2 September 1984
    - Washington Times [inside labels: Cambodia 1985, Musical], 1 January 1985
    - Cambodian Special/Bill Chewning, Mutual Radion News (WAGE-AM), 1 April 1985
    - Bell's Ladies, n.d.
    - Concord, n.d.
    - Side 1 Acapulco interview with Mazza/Side 2 Kennedy Airport and Oatlands, n.d.
    - Sound Track for Africa Slide Show, CNI World News (copy), n.d.
    - UPI Roundtable, n.d.
    - Outtakes-LaRouche, n.d.
    - Behind the Scenes w/Claire Kincannon: Killing Fields/LaRouche Act n.d.
    - LaRouche, n.d.
  - Recordings (titles taken directly from reel-to-reel tape boxes)
    - John Glenn Flight/ Funks Corn, 1 January 1958
    - Reflections Africa 1974 Vol. 1, 1 January 1974
    - Reflections Africa 1974 Vol. 2, 1 January 1974
    - Reflections #1 Africa, 1 January 1974
    - Reflections #2 Africa, 1 January 1974
    - UPI Africa Interview 1, WAGE 1974/Chewning in Kenya and Tanzania, 1 January 1974
    - UPI Africa Interview 2, WAGE 1974/Chewning in Kenya and Tanzania, 1 January 1974
    - Slide Show, CNI News, "China 1978", 1 January 1978
    - CNI Podium, Death of Jomo Kenyatta, 26 August 1978
    - CNI Podium, Andrew Young, UN, 10 March 1979
    - CNI Podium, Drug Use Abroad, Barbara Watson, State Dept, 12 May 1979
    - China and Far East/Richard Holbrooke, CNI, 26 May 1979
    - CNI Podium, Secretary of State Haig, 7 June 1981
    - CNI Podium, Secretary of State Haig, 7 June 1981
    - CNI International Spotlight, Elephant Project, East Africa, n.d.
    - CNI Podium (Central King/Express), n.d.
    - Untitled, n.d.
  - Recordings (titles taken directly from reel-to-reel tape boxes)
    - 5-71 Year End, 1 July 1971
    - Year End 1971 Vol. 2, 31 December 1971
    - Year End 1971 Vol. 4, 31 December 1971
    - 1972 Year End [2], 31 December 1972
    - Year End Vol. 1-2 1972, 31 December 1972
    - Auto Train - Senate Hearing - Loudoun Independent Party 1973, 1 January 1973
    - Year End 1973 Vol. 5, 11-2-1973--12-22-73, 22 December 1973
    - 1973 Local Review, 31 December 1973
    - 1973 Vol. 3 Year End, 31 December 1973
    - Year End 1973 Vol. 2, 31 December 1973
    - Year End 1973 Vol. 4, 31 December 1973
    - 1974 Year End Vol. 2, 4-19-74--7-26-74, 26 July 1974
    - Year End 1974 Vol. 3, 8-2-74 -- 9-27-74, 27 September 1974
    - Loudoun Year End, 10/74-11/74, 30 November 1974
    - 1974 Year end, 11-15-74 -- 12-27-75, 27 December 1974
    - 1974 Year End Vol. 1, 31 December 1974
    - Year End Review 1974, 31 December 1974
    - General Assembly 1975, 8 January 1975
    - 1975 Year End Vol. 1, 1-3-75--2-21-75, 21 February 1975
    - 1975 Year End Vol. 2, 2-28-75--4-11-75, 11 April 1975
    - Year End 1975 Vol. 3, and 4-11, 6-20, 20 June 1975
    - Year End Reports 6-20-75 to 8-22-75 Vol. 4, 22 August 1975
    - 1976 VA XGR, 1 January 1976
    - 1977 Legislative Master Vol. 1, 21 February 1977
    - 1977 XGR Master, 22 February 1977
    - XGR News Con, 7 March 1977
    - 1978 VA XGR Master Vol. 2, 1 January 1978
    - 1978 VA XGR News Con, 1 January 1978
    - Draisey General Assembly Actualities Vol. 1 1978, 1 January 1978
    - 1979 VA XGR Master Greg Hicks, 1 January 1979
    - VA XGR 1980 Vol. 2, 2/8-Cuts 29-, 8 February 1979
    - 1980 VA XGR J Berman 1/8-2/8 cuts 1-28, 8 February 1980
    - VA XGR 1980 Master Vol. 3, 2/29 -, Cuts 61-, 29 February 1980
  - Recordings (titles taken directly from reel-to-reel tape boxes)
    - Year End Actualities, 30 October 1975
    - 1975 Year End Acts - Final Vol., 31 December 1975
    - Vol 2 Year End Actualities 1975, 31 December 1975
    - Year End Actuality Vol. 4 1975, 31 December 1975
    - Vol. 2 Actuality Tape, 3-10-76 to 4/28/76, 28 April 1976
    - Vol. 4 Actuality Tape 1976, 6-3-76 to 7-26-76, 26 July 1976
    - Actuality Tape Vol 5 1976, 7 September 1976
    - Year End Actuality Tape Vol. 6 1976, 9-7-76 to 10-31-76, 31 October 1976
    - Year End Actuality Tape Vol. 7, 11-1-76 to 12-13-76, 13 December 1976
    - Year End Actuality Tape Vol. 8, 12-13-76 to 12-29-76, 29 December 1976
    - Vol. 3 Year End Actuality Tape 1976, 31 December 1976
    - Year End Actuality Tape Vol. 1 1976, 31 December 1976
    - Year End Actuality Tape Vol. 1, 2/22/77, 22 February 1977
    - Year End Actuality Tape Vol. 2 1977, 2-22-77 tape 3-24-77, 24 March 1977
    - Actualities Master Tape Vol. 3 1977, 25 April 1977
    - 1977 Actualities Vol. 4, 4-26-77 6-11-11, 11 June 1977
    - Vol. 5 (1977) Actuality Master, June 11 to July 4, 4 July 1977
    - Actuality Master Tape, Vol. 6, July 5, 1977 to July 22, 1977, 22 July 1977
    - Actuality Tape (master) July 22-Aug.4 Volume 7 (1977), 4 August 1977
    - Actuality Master Tape Vol. 8, Aug 4-29/1977, 29 August 1977
    - Actuality Master Tape Vol. 9 1977, Aug 27 to Sept 27, 27 September 1977
    - Actuality Master Tape Vol 10, September 27 to October 31, 1977, 31 October 1977
    - Actuality Master Tape, Vol. 10/11, October 31st through December 6 1977, 6 December 1977
    - Actuality Master Tape Vol. 11, December 7th to December 22nd 1977 22 December 1977
    - Actuality Master Tape Vol. 12, 12-22-77 through 1/12/78, 12 January 1978
    - 1978 Actuality Master Tape Vol. 1, Jan. 16 through Feb. 10, 10 February 1978
    - Actuality Master Tape Vol. 2 1978, Feb.11th through March 15th, 15 March 1978
    - Actuality Master Tape Vol. 3, March 16, 1978 through April 7, 1978, 7 April 1978
    - Actuality Master Vol. 4 1978, 4-7--5/6, 6 May 1978
    - Actuality Master Vol. 5 1978, 5-6--5-16, 16 May 1978
    - Actuality Master Vol. 6 1978, 5-16--5-26, 26 May 1978
    - Actuality Master Vol. 7 1978, 5-26--6-2, 2 June 1978
    - Actuality Master Vol. 8 1978, 6-3--6-22, 22 June 1978
  - Recordings (titles taken directly from reel-to-reel tape boxes)
    - Actuality Master Vol. 9 1978, 6-22--7-12, 12 July 1978
    - Actuality Master Vol. 10 1978, 7/12-7/18, 18 July 1978
    - Actuality Master Vol. 11 1978, 7-18--7/22, 22 July 1978
    - Actuality Master Tape Vol. 12 1978, 7/28--9/27, 27 September 1978
    - Actuality Master Vol. 13 1978, 9-28--12-5, 5 December 1978
    - Actuality Master Vol. 14 1978, 12-5--12-31, 31 December 1978
    - Actuality Master 1979, Vol. 1, 1-1979-4/1/79, 1 April 1979
    - Actuality Master 1979, Vol. 2, 4/1-5/31 cuts 122-233, 31 May 1979
    - Actuality Master Vol. 3 1978, 5/31/79 to 7/5/79 cut 234 to 285, 5 July 1979
    - Actuality Master 1979 Vol. 4, cuts 286-336, 7/5-7/22, 22 July 1979
    - Actuality Master 1979 Vol. 5, 337-378, 9/21-11/14, 14 November 1979
    - Actuality Master Vol. 6 1979, cuts 379-411, 11-17-12/31, 31 December 1979
    - Master 1980 Vol. 1, cuts 1-86 1/1-2/3, 3 February 1980
    - Master Vol. 2. 1980, cuts 37-63, 2/3-3/6, 6 March 1980
    - Master Vol. 3 1980, cuts 64-95, 3/8-3/25, 25 March 1980
    - Master 1980 Vol. 4, 3/26-4/10 cuts 95-125, 10 April 1980
    - Master Vol. 5, 4-11-80--4-17-80, cuts 126-145, 17 April 1980
    - 1980 Master Vol. 6, 4/17-4/29 146-175, 29 April 1980
    - 1980 Master Vol. 7, 4-30 -- 5-8 176-205, 8 May 1980
    - 1980 master Vol. 8, 5/8-5/24 #206-232 24 May 1980
    - 1980 master Vol. 9, 5/24-6/10 cuts 233-271, 10 June 1980
    - 1980 master Vol. 10, cuts 272-330, 6/10/80-7/23/80, 23 July 1980
    - Master - 1980 Vol. 11, 7/23-8/22 cuts 331-366, 22 August 1980
    - 1980 Master Vol. 12, 8/22-9/11/80 cuts 367-411, 11 September 1980
    - Actuality Master Vol. 13, 9/11/80-10/15/80 cuts 412-448, 15 October 1980
    - Vol. 14, Cuts 449-490, 10/15/80--11/7/80, 7 November 1980
    - Vol. 15, 11/7/80-11/25/80, cuts 491-533, 25 November 1980
    - Vol. 15, 11/7/80-11/25/80, cuts 491-533, 25 November 1980
    - Vol. 16/17, 535-572, 11/25-12/15/80, 15 December 1980
    - Actuality Master Vol. 21, 2/11/81, 11 February 1981
    - Actuality Master Vol. 22, Feb 19th, 19 February 1981
    - Actuality Master Vol. 25, 3/21/81-3/30/81, 30 March 1981
    - Vol. 27, 4/81 ACT TAPE, 1 April 1981
    - Vol. 26, March 31-April 11 (1981), 11 April 1981
    - Actuality details for 2/19-3/3, n.d.
    - Vol. 28, n.d.
    - Vol. 29, n.d.
  - Recordings (titles taken directly from reel-to-reel tape boxes)
    - Vol. 31, 1 June 1981
    - Vol. 32, June 81, 1 June 1981
    - Vol. 30, May-June 81, 30 June 1981
    - Vol. 35, 8/10-8/19, 19 August 1981
    - Vol. 36, 8/18-9/12, 12 September 1981
    - Vol. 37, 9/11 to 10/9 tape 1, 9 October 1981
    - Vol. 38, 10/9 to [blank], tape 2, 9 November 1981
    - Vol. 39, 11/10 to 11/19, 19 November 1981
    - Vol. 40, 11-23 to 12-11-81, 11 December 1981
    - Vol. 41, 12-11-81 to 12-17-81, 17 December 1981
    - Vol. 42, 12-21-81 to 12/31/81 Year's End, 31 December 1981
    - Vol. 43, 12/31/81 to 1/13/83, 13 January 1982
    - 27 January 1982 27 January 1982
    - Vol. 45, 1/26-2/15 '82, 15 February 1982
    - Vol. 46, 2/15 to 3/10/82, 10 March 1982
    - Vol. 47, 3/10/ to 4/2/82, 2 April 1982
    - Vol. 48, 22 April 1982
    - Vol. 49, 4/23 to 4/28, 28 April 1982
    - Vol. 49, [sic 50] 4/28 - 5/5, 5 May 1982